wachoviacreditcards.com 2011-11-02

# Wachovia Security Plus(SM) Customer Center - Privacy and Security Practices

## Keeping Your Information Safe and Secure

**Highlights of Our Commitment to You**

  * We do not sell customer information to third parties. 
  * We do not share customer information with outside parties who may wish to market their products to you. 
  * We safeguard your customer information carefully. 
  * We are committed to protecting your customer information in every transaction, at every level of our organization. 
  * We are committed to helping you protect your privacy every day. 

Privacy Statement **_  
_** The Privacy Policy for Wells Fargo and Wachovia Companies describes how we use and protect customer information. You have choices about how we share your information within Wells Fargo and Wachovia and how we contact you for marketing purposes. 

Security Statement ** _  
_**Wachovia understands that your trust in us depends on how well we keep your personal, business, and account information secure. We go to great lengths to see that your transactions and personally identifiable information are confidential, secure, and protected from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. The Security Statement describes the technology that keeps personal information private and how you can help protect this information. 

Internet Privacy Statement **_  
_** Wachovia's commitment to protect your information and your privacy extends to our online products and services. While our privacy policies are the same no matter how you chose to visit Wachovia, we have extra measures in place to protect your privacy when you come to us online. The Internet Privacy Statement describes the Internet-specific privacy practices governing wachovia.com and its use by consumers.
